<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/</link><description>Recent content on TalentCLEF</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Task Organizers</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</guid><description> Luis Gascó, PhD. Avature, Spain Hermenegildo Fabregat, PhD. Avature, Spain Laura García-Sardiña Avature, Spain Daniel Deniz Cerpa, PhD. Avature, Spain Paula Estrella Avature, Spain Alvaro Rodrigo, PhD. UNED, Spain Rabih Zbib, PhD. Avature, Spain</description></item><item><title>Task Organizers</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/people/task_organizers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/people/task_organizers/</guid><description> Task A Luis Gascó, PhD. Avature, Spain Hermenegildo Fabregat, PhD. Avature, Spain Laura García-Sardiña Avature, Spain Daniel Deniz Cerpa, PhD. Avature, Spain Paula Estrella Avature, Spain Casimiro Pío Carrino Avature, Spain Alvaro Rodrigo, PhD. UNED, Spain Rabih Zbib, PhD. Avature, Spain Task B Jens-Joris Decorte TechWolf Matthias De Lange, PhD. TechWolf Luis Gascó, PhD. Avature, Spain</description></item><item><title>Description of the Corpus</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. This page contains the corpus information for TalentCLEF 2025 tasks. You can access the link to download in datasets page.
Task A: Multilingual Job Title Matching Corpus Summary: The corpus used for Task A consists of a set of job titles in three languages: English, Spanish and German, from different job domains and professional sectors.</description></item><item><title>Description of the Corpus</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/description_corpus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/description_corpus/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. This page contains the corpus information for TalentCLEF 2026 tasks. You can access the link to download in datasets page.</description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The data will be hosted on the Zenodo platform under the NLP in HR community, following the file structure outlined below. Each time new data is added, an updated version of the dataset will be published on the platform.</description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/datasets/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The data will be hosted on the Zenodo platform under the NLP in HR community, following the file structure outlined below. Each time new data is added, an updated version of the dataset will be published on the platform.</description></item><item><title>Scientific Committee</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</guid><description> Eneko Agirre - Full Professor of the University of the Basque Country UPV/EHU - ACL Fellow David Camacho - Full Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Debora Nozza - Assistant Professor of Bocconi University Jens-Joris Decorte - Lead AI Scientist at TechWolf David Graus - Lead Data Scientist at Randstad Group Mesutt Kayaa - Postdoctoral Researcher at Jobindex A/S and IT University Copenhagen Jan Luts - Senior Data Scientist at NTT Data &amp;amp; ESCO Elena Montiel-Ponsoda - Professor at the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) - AI4Labour project Javier Huertas Tato - Assistant Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Patricia Martín Chozas - Postdoctoral Researcher at the Ontology Engineering Group (UPM) - AI4Labour project</description></item><item><title>Scientific Committee</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/people/scientific_committee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/people/scientific_committee/</guid><description>The Scientific Committee will be announced soon.</description></item><item><title>TalentCLEF 2025 Workshop Schedule</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/workshop/workshop_schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/workshop/workshop_schedule/</guid><description>Thursday 11 September 14:15-15:45 Session 1 Welcome Overview of the TalentCLEF 2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management
Luis Gasco, Hermenegildo Fabregat, Laura García-Sardiña, Paula Estrella, Daniel Deniz, Álvaro Rodrigo, Rabih Zbib AlexU-NLP at TalentCLEF 2025: Curriculum-Driven Hybrid Retrieval for Multilingual Job Title Matching
Rana Barakat, Omar Mokhtar, Marwan Torki, Nagwa Elmakky UDII-UPM at TalentCLEF 2025: Task A - Multilingual Job Title Matching
Javier Rodríguez-Vidal, Ascensión López-Vargas, Pablo Manuel Vigara Gallego, Francisco Javier Del Álamo, Ángel García-Beltrán VerbaNex at TalentCLEF2025: Semantic Matching of Multilingual Job Titles through a Framework Integrating ESCO Taxonomy Melissa Moreno Novoa, Juan Carlos Martinez-Santos, Jairo Serrano, Edwin Puertas Multilingual Job Title Matching with MPNet-Based Sentence Transformers Adam Brikman, Michael Sana, Holden Ruegger A Two-Stage Multilingual Job Title Matching System: Combining Expert Knowledge and LLM-based Ranking</description></item><item><title>Additional resources</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</guid><description>To support your participation in this shared task, we have compiled a list of additional resources that may be useful for understanding the task better, exploring related work, and utilizing domain-specific models.
1. Related papers: Gasco, L., Fabregat, H., García-Sardiña, L., Deniz, D., Rodrigo, A., Estrella, P., &amp;amp; Zbib, R. (2025, April). TalentCLEF at CLEF2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management. In European Conference on Information Retrieval (pp.</description></item><item><title>Additional resources</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/additional_resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/additional_resources/</guid><description>To support your participation in this shared task, we have compiled a list of additional resources that may be useful for understanding the task better, exploring related work, and utilizing domain-specific models.
1. Related papers: Gasco, L., Fabregat, H., García-Sardiña, L., Deniz, D., Rodrigo, A., Estrella, P., &amp;amp; Zbib, R. (2025, April). TalentCLEF at CLEF2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management. In European Conference on Information Retrieval (pp.</description></item><item><title>Evaluation info</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/evaluation_info/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/evaluation_info/</guid><description>The evaluation for TalentCLEF-2025 will be conducted on Codabench. Submissions will be ranked using Mean Average Precision (MAP).
TalentCLEF Task A - Codabench TalentCLEF Task B - Codabench Evaluation dates Task A: Start Date: 21st April 2025 End Date: 5th May 2025 Task B: Start Date: 28st April 2025 End Date: 5th May 2025 Evaluation Criteria The top-performing teams will be determined based on the following evaluation criteria:
Task A:</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/publications/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/publications/</guid><description>Links to the CEUR Proceedings here Overview paper Please, cite: Luis Gasco, Hermenegildo Fabregat, Laura García-Sardiña, Paula Estrella, Daniel Deniz, Álvaro Rodrigo and Rabih Zbib. 2025. Overview of the TalentCLEF 2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management. In International Conference of the Cross-Language Evaluation Forum for European Languages. Springer. [View preprint on arXiv] [View Springer paper] BibTeX citation: @inproceedings{gasco2025overview, title={{Overview of the TalentCLEF 2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management}}, author={Gasco, Luis and Fabregat, Hermenegildo and Garc\'{\i}a-Sardi{\~n}a, Laura and Estrella, Paula and Deniz, Daniel and Rodrigo, \'{A}lvaro and Zbib, Rabih}, booktitle={{Experimental IR Meets Multilinguality, Multimodality, and Interaction}}, publisher={{Springer Nature Switzerland}}, address={{Cham}}, pages={{464--485}}, isbn={{978-3-032-04354-2}}, year={2025}, } 📋 Copy Copied!</description></item><item><title>Submission format</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/submission_format/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/submission_format/</guid><description>You can find a tutorial on the process of generating submission files and evaluating them in the Tutorials section of the Additional resources page Submissions must adhere to the TREC Run File Format, including column names, with exactly six space-separated columns per line, structured as follows:
&amp;lt;q_id&amp;gt; Q0 &amp;lt;doc_id&amp;gt; &amp;lt;rank&amp;gt; &amp;lt;score&amp;gt; &amp;lt;run_tag&amp;gt; Column Descriptions
&amp;lt;q_id&amp;gt;: The identifier for the query corresponding to the job title being searched. Q0: A constant placeholder (always set to &amp;ldquo;Q0&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Task A Results</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/task_a_results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/task_a_results/</guid><description> Below you will find the official results for Task A of TalentCLEF. This section provides both a graphical overview and a detailed table of the full results. The interactive visualizations are designed to help you explore and analyze the performance of participating systems based on different criteria. For further details or questions regarding the evaluation, please refer to the official publication or contact the organizers.
Graphical representation Table</description></item><item><title>Task B Results</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/task_b_results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/results/task_b_results/</guid><description> Below you will find the official results for Task B of TalentCLEF. This section provides both a graphical overview and a detailed table of the full results. The interactive visualizations are designed to help you explore and analyze the performance of participating systems based on different criteria. For further details or questions regarding the evaluation, please refer to the official publication or contact the organizers.
Graphical representation Table</description></item><item><title>Codabench</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/codabench/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/evaluation/codabench/</guid><description>The evaluation will take place on Codabench, where participants must upload their predictions according to the submission format. The official competition links will be shared soon through this platform and online communication channels.
Task A - Codabench rules For Task A, predictions for each language pair must be generated in separate .trec files. These files should be compressed into a ZIP file, ensuring that the files are placed directly inside the archive (without any folders), and then uploaded to Codabench.</description></item><item><title>Announcing the First TalentCLEF Workshop @ CLEF 2025</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2025/09/05/announcing-the-first-talentclef-workshop-@-clef-2025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2025/09/05/announcing-the-first-talentclef-workshop-@-clef-2025/</guid><description>After a year of hard work and great participation, I’m excited to share that the first TalentCLEF Workshop will be held at #CLEF2025 in Madrid on September 11–12, 2025
TalentCLEF has been an incredible community effort to push forward research on multilingual HR–NLP solutions for skill and job title intelligence, tackling real challenges in talent management.
This year’s program includes 15 talks from the teams that took part in the evaluation campaign, showcasing innovative approaches to the tasks we set.</description></item><item><title>Release of Sample Set for TalentCLEF 2025</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/10/25/release-of-sample-set-for-talentclef-2025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/10/25/release-of-sample-set-for-talentclef-2025/</guid><description>We are thrilled to announce the release of the sample set for the TalentCLEF 2025! This sample dataset serves as an essential resource for participants to familiarize themselves with the format, scope, and types of data they will encounter in the TalentCLEF tasks.
The sample set provides a practical preview, allowing participants to explore the dataset structure and begin preliminary analyses in preparation for the workshop. The release includes detailed documentation including a Corpus Description and the Dataset Format</description></item><item><title>Presentation of TalentCLEF Task at CLEF2024 in Grenoble</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/09/19/presentation-of-talentclef-task-at-clef2024-in-grenoble/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/09/19/presentation-of-talentclef-task-at-clef2024-in-grenoble/</guid><description>Last week, on September 12, we presented the TalentCLEF Task at the CLEF2024 conference in Grenoble. This session provided an interesting opportunity to showcase the objectives, structure and expected impact of the task, generating a great deal of interest among researchers and practitioners alike.
The presentation highlighted the various facets of the TalentCLEF Task, including the unique challenges it addresses, the dataset design, and the evaluation criteria that participants will navigate.</description></item><item><title>Release of TalentCLEF website</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/08/29/release-of-talentclef-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/08/29/release-of-talentclef-website/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the launch of the new TalentCLEF workshop website!
The website is designed to be a comprehensive resource for participants and researchers interested in the upcoming TalentCLEF 2025 workshop, providing an easy access to essential information about the event, including detailed descriptions of the workshop&amp;rsquo;s goals, schedule, and registration process.
You can track all the details about the TalentCLEF task in the task item, including the schedule, summary of the tasks, and new information about the data and evaluation criteria will be published soon.</description></item><item><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/about/</guid><description>TalentCLEF What is TalentCLEF? TalentCLEF is an initiative to advance Natural Language Processing (NLP) in Human Capital Management (HCM). It aims to create a public benchmark for model evaluation and promote collaboration to develop fair, multilingual, and flexible systems that improve Human Resources (HR) practices across different industries. Join us in this innovative journey to shape the future of HR technology. What challenges does TalentCLEF address? Multilingualism Developing systems that can accurately handle multiple languages to manage global and diverse employee needs.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>