<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/</link><description>Recent content on TalentCLEF</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Task Organizers</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</guid><description> Luis Gascó, PhD. Avature, Spain Hermenegildo Fabregat, PhD. Avature, Spain Laura García-Sardiña Avature, Spain Alvaro Rodrigo, PhD. UNED, Spain Rabih Zbib, PhD. Avature, Spain</description></item><item><title>Description of the Corpus</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The specific details about the dataset will be published when the sample set is published.</description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The specific details about the dataset will be published when the sample set is published.</description></item><item><title>Scientific Committee</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</guid><description> Eneko Agirre - Full Professor of the University of the Basque Country UPV/EHU - ACL Fellow David Camacho - Full Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Debora Nozza - Assistant Professor of Bocconi University Jens-Joris Decorte - Lead AI Scientist at TechWolf David Graus - Lead Data Scientist at Randstad Group Mesutt Kayaa - Postdoctoral Researcher at Jobindex A/S and IT University Copenhagen Elena Montiel-Ponsoda - Professor at the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) - AI4Labour project Javier Huertas Tato - Assistant Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Patricia Martín Chozas - Postdoctoral Researcher at the Ontology Engineering Group (UPM) - AI4Labour project</description></item><item><title>Additional resources</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</guid><description>To support your participation in this shared task, we have compiled a list of additional resources that may be useful for understanding the task better, exploring related work, and utilizing domain-specific models.
1. Related papers: Zbib, R., Lacasa, L. A., Retyk, F., Poves, R., Aizpuru, J., Fabregat, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; García-Casademont, E. (2022). Learning Job Titles Similarity from Noisy Skill Labels. arXiv preprint arXiv:2207.00494 Decorte, J. J., Van Hautte, J., Demeester, T.</description></item><item><title>Easy documentation with Docsy</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/blog/2018/10/06/easy-documentation-with-docsy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/blog/2018/10/06/easy-documentation-with-docsy/</guid><description>This is a typical blog post that includes images.
The front matter specifies the date of the blog post, its title, a short description that will be displayed on the blog landing page, and its author.
Including images Here&amp;rsquo;s an image (featured-sunset-get.png) that includes a byline and a caption.
Fetch and scale an image in the upcoming Hugo 0.43. Photo: Riona MacNamara / CC-BY-CA The front matter of this post specifies properties to be assigned to all image resources:</description></item><item><title>Second blog post</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/blog/2018/10/06/second-blog-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/blog/2018/10/06/second-blog-post/</guid><description>Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.
There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.
There should be no margin above this first sentence.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talent_clef/about/</guid><description>TalentCLEF What is TalentCLEF? TalentCLEF is an initiative focused on advancing the application of Natural Language Processing (NLP) technologies in Human Capital Management (HCM). By establishing a public benchmark for model evaluation and fostering a collaborative environment, TalentCLEF seeks to create fair, multilingual, and adaptable systems that enhance HR practices across industries. Join us in this innovative journey to shape the future of HR technology. What challenges TalentCLEF address? Multilingualism Developing systems that can accurately handle multiple languages to manage global and diverse employee needs.</description></item></channel></rss>