<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/</link><description>Recent content on TalentCLEF</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Task Organizers</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/task_organizers/</guid><description> Luis Gascó, PhD. Avature, Spain Hermenegildo Fabregat, PhD. Avature, Spain Laura García-Sardiña Avature, Spain Alvaro Rodrigo, PhD. UNED, Spain Rabih Zbib, PhD. Avature, Spain</description></item><item><title>Description of the Corpus</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/description_corpus/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The specific details about the dataset will be published when the sample set is published.</description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/datasets/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The specific details about the dataset will be published when the sample set is published.</description></item><item><title>Scientific Committee</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/people/scientific_committee/</guid><description> Eneko Agirre - Full Professor of the University of the Basque Country UPV/EHU - ACL Fellow David Camacho - Full Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Debora Nozza - Assistant Professor of Bocconi University Jens-Joris Decorte - Lead AI Scientist at TechWolf David Graus - Lead Data Scientist at Randstad Group Mesutt Kayaa - Postdoctoral Researcher at Jobindex A/S and IT University Copenhagen Elena Montiel-Ponsoda - Professor at the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) - AI4Labour project Javier Huertas Tato - Assistant Professor of the Technical University of Madrid (UPM) Patricia Martín Chozas - Postdoctoral Researcher at the Ontology Engineering Group (UPM) - AI4Labour project</description></item><item><title>Additional resources</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2025/data/additional_resources/</guid><description>To support your participation in this shared task, we have compiled a list of additional resources that may be useful for understanding the task better, exploring related work, and utilizing domain-specific models.
1. Related papers: Zbib, R., Lacasa, L. A., Retyk, F., Poves, R., Aizpuru, J., Fabregat, H., &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; García-Casademont, E. (2022). Learning Job Titles Similarity from Noisy Skill Labels. arXiv preprint arXiv:2207.00494 Decorte, J. J., Van Hautte, J., Demeester, T.</description></item><item><title>Release of TalentCLEF website</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/08/29/release-of-talentclef-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/blog/2024/08/29/release-of-talentclef-website/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the launch of the new TalentCLEF workshop website!
The website is designed to be a comprehensive resource for participants and researchers interested in the upcoming TalentCLEF 2025 workshop, providing an easy access to essential information about the event, including detailed descriptions of the workshop&amp;rsquo;s goals, schedule, and registration process.
You can track all the details about the TalentCLEF task in the task item, including the schedule, summary of the tasks, and new information about the data and evaluation criteria will be published soon.</description></item><item><title>TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/about/</guid><description>TalentCLEF What is TalentCLEF? TalentCLEF is an initiative to advance Natural Language Processing (NLP) in Human Capital Management (HCM). It aims to create a public benchmark for model evaluation and promote collaboration to develop fair, multilingual, and flexible systems that improve Human Resources (HR) practices across different industries. Join us in this innovative journey to shape the future of HR technology. What challenges does TalentCLEF address? Multilingualism Developing systems that can accurately handle multiple languages to manage global and diverse employee needs.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>