<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data on TalentCLEF</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/</link><description>Recent content in Data on TalentCLEF</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Description of the Corpus</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/description_corpus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/description_corpus/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. This page contains the corpus information for TalentCLEF 2026 tasks. You can access the link to download in datasets page.</description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/datasets/</guid><description>We take the legal and ethical implications of using AI in Human Resources very seriously. It is important to note that the data we utilize inherently excludes any personal information, focusing solely on job titles and skills without involving personal/company information or geographic location. The data will be hosted on the Zenodo platform under the NLP in HR community, following the file structure outlined below. Each time new data is added, an updated version of the dataset will be published on the platform.</description></item><item><title>Additional resources</title><link>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/additional_resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://talentclef.github.io/talentclef/docs/talentclef-2026/data/additional_resources/</guid><description>To support your participation in this shared task, we have compiled a list of additional resources that may be useful for understanding the task better, exploring related work, and utilizing domain-specific models.
1. Related papers: Gasco, L., Fabregat, H., García-Sardiña, L., Deniz, D., Rodrigo, A., Estrella, P., &amp;amp; Zbib, R. (2025, April). TalentCLEF at CLEF2025: Skill and Job Title Intelligence for Human Capital Management. In European Conference on Information Retrieval (pp.</description></item></channel></rss>